[{"answer": "Yes, that can happen.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How does that work now with this decision?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Oh, I do.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Do you think he will feel justice was served?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I think they did.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Did Ravi's tweets nail him?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "This is only a trial decision.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "So, when we look back one day at this like it was Brown versus Board of Education for social media, will this be a precedent, Lisa?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Most states do have hate crime laws.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "You want to explain?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "The most importance thing I tell parents, not what they tell themselves.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Kids who are bullied, kids who are bullies, what should we as parents be telling their children?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "He -- there's some conversation he had with him that still is unknown.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Did Ravi try to apologize but we think the message never got to Clementi?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Doing great.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "How you guys doing?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "She's beautiful.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Doesn't she look wonderful, man?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Doing an interview like this.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "ALL: Together doing an interview?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Well, I saw -- you know, we were at a party, at a club, and we had just finished final exams.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "How did you meet?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Back then, you go to the freak or you go down to the floor, and she could really do it.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What was the dance back then?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "She could drop it like it was hot before you were dropping it like it was hot?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, you know, after we met, we went on our separate ways.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "You want to take it from there, baby?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Not yet.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Did he have a specific reputation as a ladies' man?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I think, Arsenio it was just the way she carried herself.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "But what was it about, that conversation?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "And, yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "But I watched you.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Come on, man.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Why did you play it that way?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Well, you know what it was, it was comfort, there was a comfort level.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Was there a moment where you looked at him, and felt -- I could go the distance with this man?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Back then?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Twice, yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Twice?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Do you remember either of the reasons for calling the engagement off?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "No, he didn't do anything wrong.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "What did he do wrong?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Am I saying it right?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "We were at home in our office, in our den area, yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Where were you when he first told you that he was HIV positive?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Yes, he was like in Denver or somewhere, yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "He was supposed to be playing and you get a call from a guy who should be in the warm-up doing layups?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Arsenio, the worst ride of my life, because when you make a mistake, it actually hurts other people.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "What was that ride like to her, to give her this news?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Now, you had just found out like two days ago?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Right, Cookie?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I was like, devastated.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "What did you do in that moment when he said it to you?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "In the movie -- ESPN 33's announcement, I think there's a moment where you joked and said, I thought maybe he wanted a divorce.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "People joked about it, but nobody really you knew really had it, you know?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "No, we had such a hard time, back and forth, engagement, getting married.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "You had no idea?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "A little harder than that.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Like a \"Days of Our Lives\" soap opera tap?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Did you even feel it?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Dr. Ho, he's the acclaimed researcher of AIDS in this country?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "And by the way, all of this happened because of an insurance medical test?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Did you lose friends?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "But there were problems.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Never an argument?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "It's amazing.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "You know what I mean?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Well, it's going to be a play about Larry and I, our life on the basketball court and away from the court as well.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Tell me about this play?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "I think I'm -- Arsenio, I'm a big baseball fan.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "What would make you look in the opposite direction from that sport and say, I want that now?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "I created this jean for a women with curves.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Where did that come from?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "When a woman is frustrated and it's your wife, you as the husband get that frustration.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "So I thought why not create a jean with that style, with those styling, with the premium qualities, that fit a woman with a curve?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Yes, CJByCookieJohnson.com.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Go online, you have a website?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Without a doubt it changed politics forever.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Do you think it changed politics forever?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Well, let me answer the question, then I have one for you.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Don't you think so?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Well, at that time, because he was a governor, I didn't really see the magnitude of what could happen.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "Piers, my question to you is how did you pull it off?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "The country is fractured and the Republican party, at the moment, is fractured into a number of different groups.", "docId": "120316pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "Why is politics so mean this year?", "qSentId": 757}]